uh the main goal of the game is to reach
the city mall the largest location
suitable for building a
base uh it has multiple sections
including some underground areas and
there is a potential to Electrify it and
to build defense structures
so the player must pass through V
various biomes filled with uh hostile
creatures and cultists and of course
there will be a harsh weather on on the
way there um the city mall is located in
the kind of very very treacherous biome
which is known as the white hell so
players will need to explore the world
first to prepare for this
journey uh and and there will be some
unknown dangers in the city mall
itself uh in terms of gameplay time a
player focusing solely on the main
storyline can complete the game in
around 8 hours roughly uh those
interested in exploring optional
locations and fully developing their
character can expect around 18 hours of
gameplay and for
completionists that's aim to explore
every location and unlock every
activity and search every chest and
search through every cave Etc then the
game
offers
approximately 30 hours of Total play
time but the game is based on on the
sandbox
principle and the cooperation with up to
four players online in C mode is also
very important
so if someone wants to stay longer in
the world and
continue uh for example building bases
renovating
places and so on the the limit is just
your creativity
basically uh the game features uh
Cooperative gameplay co-op mode allowing
up to four players to form a group
uh one player creates a
server and the server can be totally
public or can be private that means you
can set up a password and only share the
password with your
friends and players in co- mode they
progress through the game together they
can focus on the main quest or they can
simply survive in the in the
post-apocalyptic dangerous Frozen
Wasteland um most of the time you will
be adventuring with
friends but uh as as I said you can join
other players with open servers and just
help them survive so it is fine to play
with friends but it's is also perfectly
okay to find the server and join if it's
an open server and play with uh someone
you don't know so the world and the game
is designed for
cooperation more players usually mean
there's a better chances of
[Music]
survival yes of course the full version
of permafrost will include support for
the Chinese
language uh we are working with that
right now but as with any language a lot
of work is needed
because we want the every language
version to be uh to be perfect for for
the best possible
experience um first of all exploration
in
permafrost is uh is more Vari than in
any other
games so many titles focus on just one
environment like like it's just a forest
just desert and so on and we from the
beginning we designed and we have
created
a immersive world when players can
explore forests suburbs a industrial
areas urban areas even
skyscrapers so the unique
feature is also ability to try
vertically so you not only explore the
surface but also go into the caves into
underground areas and also
go uh you can also explore skyscrapers
vertically uh challenges like uh super
cold regions or destroyed
environments it will require players to
use gameplay mechanics to overcome the
these difficulties and also there are
new Transportation methods for example a
slay that will serve both as a mean of
transport and as a mobile
storage another aspect of the game is
renovation and free building so you can
you can experience uh free building
feature in our demo uh player can freely
players can freely build their own bases
uh but also they can renovate existing
structures which is a feature that will
be available in the full game
and you basically can go to destroy the
building and renovate it restore it to
the to their previous
Glory uh that gives in our in our
opinion a unique choice you can either
use free building or you can renovate uh
existing
buildings you can choose what fits your
gameplay Style and What Makes you uh
what makes better fun with the game for
you
um another feature of the game is is
cooperation the game was designed with
uh cop mode from the
start it is a fun game to play in single
mode but uh cop mode is not just a
addition to the game it is like a core
feature of the
game we
also did kind of unique approach to the
story we want to introduce players to a
reach world full of history and full of
lore and there are many Hidden Truths to
uncover uh there is a set of unique
characters that you can meet in the
world uh and players will face impactful
choices like really impactful the world
will react to their
actions for for example if you renovate
a certain destroyed building then people
will come to it and maybe there will be
Traders there will be no interactions
trading and so
on the companion will be developed uh uh
throughout Early Access uh in time they
will find loot and bring to the player
or alert about some hostile
conditions there may be even more
companions than dogs in the future
so I'm not promising that right now but
stay tuned for updates there will be
more about the companions in the
[Music]
game so as the game progresses more
ranged weapons and enemies will be
introduced currently in the demo there
are four
Firearms uh with two additional weapons
in Early Access but uh new ones like for
example the crossbow will be added as we
continue to develop the
game uh the enemies will also evolve in
the beginning you mostly battle the cold
and the environment and maybe wild
animals but as the game progresses it
introduces more enemies human enemies
like the members of the Moon Cult
uh and they will be kind of a serious
threat in the full
[Music]
game the combat system will be expanded
over time our main focus is on creating
an immersive world and building crafting
systems but we plan to improve combat
especially Ranch
combat uh we know that players
have fun with the wrenched combat
so uh yeah we want to do this we want
players to feel like a stalkers in a
frozen post-apocalyptic
[Music]
world what are the main fixes and
quality of life improvements you will be
working on we are kind of like halfway
through implementing full controller
support custom key bindings of course
and other quality of life features we
also plan to add lots of customization
options not just a couple of difficulty
presets like you know easy normal heart
but a big set of options so anyone can
tune the game to much Personal Taste
taste and personal needs
[Music]
in Early Access players will be able to
use slays which are mobile and useful
for travel across cold areas they also
double as a mobile containers
basically and as the development
continues we plan to add a snowmobile
which is currently in early development
stage allowing for long distance
travel will you include similar ideas
like anti mines or te tin traps from The
Last of Us we will continue developing
uh traps as they connect to Major
gameplay branches like building and
crafting and
combat fighting human enemies will be
expanding during Early Access we plan to
introduce traps and defense structures
that will be specifically used against
humans
[Music]
we plan to introduce a couple of kinds
of dogs and companions in the future but
at this point in time I I can't really
confirm
exactly what will be available and
when uh the dog companion is one of our
main features so we will continue to
develop and expand this aspect of the
game
uh will there be different breeds of
dogs most likely yes most likely yes
depending of what we can develop uh with
a very very good quality